http://www.diettogo.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
Diet-to-Go is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Web site. In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the IP addresses not the e-mail addresses, of visitors.
Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer's hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation and to measure the effectiveness of our promotional placements, and is not shared with anyone other than Diet-to-Go contractors who assist us in these efforts and are bound to confidentiality. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.
In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information and products you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address. This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.
Use of Collected Information
IP address or domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information solely to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.
When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. We use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your order. This information may be shared only if necessary to fulfill your order request or for related purposes. We do not sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. So that you may receive their offers and discounts, we may share your name and email with our partners/distribution locations. Otherwise, we will release information about you only if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).
Link to Other sites
Our web site may contain links to other sites such as distributors and sales affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.
Security of Collected Information
We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those staff members who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Company employees who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action and termination.
Access to Collected Information
You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this web site by contacting us as described below.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.
Changes to This Policy
Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Web site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.
SMS Policy
By submitting an order or creating an account, you confirm that the information provided is accurate and complete and that you agree to receive email communications, phone calls, and SMS/Text Messages from Diet-to-Go at the numbers provided above, including your wireless numbers if provided. Contact methods may include calls or texts made using automated technology. You understand that your consent is not a condition of purchasing services from the company and that if you wish to order without providing the above consent, you may order by contacting the company directly at 800-743-7546.
Get Our Free Newsletter
Get free support to help you on
your weight loss journey!
SIGNUP
Thanks for signing up!
Get Your Free Diet Analysis
Are you looking for a Keto Meal Plan?
Are you Diabetic or Pre-Diabetic?
GET RESULTS
Learn MorePickup LocationsKeto DietDiet-to-Go ReviewsDiabetes MenuSuccess StoriesAbout UsAbout UsGuaranteeFood SafetyTerms of ServicePrivacy PolicyPartnershipsPartner ProgramOnline Affiliate ProgramCorporate WellnessResourcesHelpContact UsDiet-to-Go BlogLocal EventsFree Diet AnalysisCustomersMenu ManagementUpdate Plan
Copyright 2020
Diet-To-Go©
